JYOTI KUMARI

jyotisahu.kumari7@gmail.com 7739991776 C/o MR. NEM SINGH SAHU, D/108 KHUTADIH SONARI jamshedpur, Jharkhand

Summary

Highly motivated, well organized professional Tax Consultant offering over 1 year experience in Accounting. Having Kowledge of Sales reconciliations, Purchase reconciliations, GSTR reconciliations, payment processing, journal entries, data entry, billing and collections, along with 10+ Year strong communication skills, HR assiatant, Team Managing and a creative talent for cultivating rewarding relationships with customers, peers and supervisory staff. Dynamic learner with facility for rapidly mastering new modalities. Highly competent in MS Office, other various accounting programs.

Education

Jamshedpur women's College

Commerce • jamshedpur, Jharkhand

06/2008

Gradurated in Accounts Hons from Ranchi University

Skills

- advance excel
- · Customer service
- Accounts receivable
- Ecrm
- · soft skill
- MIS
- Account Management
- Internet Research
- · Data Reconciliation

- · Microsoft office
- Tally
- Accounts payable
- · Data entry
- · Team Management
- · Account Reconciliation
- Outlook
- · Data Reseach
- · GSTR Filing

Experience

S k Naredi & Co. (CA Firm)

Account Executive • jamshedpur, Jharkhand

05/2020 - Present

- GSTR-1 Filing on Behalf of Client.
- GSTR-3B Filing on Behalf of Client
- GSTR-9 Filing on Behalf of Client
- · GSTR-9C Filing on Behalf of Client
- Making Financial Records as per company requirement
- Maintaining Tally Data, Sales Entry, Purchase Entery, Journal Entry, Contra Entry, Receipt and Payment Entry.
- · Reconcilation of Sales.
- · Reconcilation of ITC
- Reconcilation of GSTR-2A
- · Reconcilation of data
- · Looking after the MIS & mails
- · Managing Team.
- Co-ordinates with all departments concerned in order to maintain Front Office functions properly

YELLOW TREE - A Boutique Living

- · Recruiting, training and supervising staff.
- · Managing budgets.
- Maintaining statistical and financial records.
- Planning maintenance work, events and room bookings.
- · Handling customer complaints and queries.
- · Promoting and marketing the business.
- Ensuring compliance with health and safety legislation and licensing laws.
- Managing staff and overseeing schedules to make sure all departments have enough employees to provide assistance to guests
- · Providing training on changes in services
- Scheduling and overseeing maintenance and repairs in individual rooms and common areas
- · Working with inspectors to ensure facility meets all requirements
- Providing customer service and accommodating clients who need extra assistance
- Checks on registration cards of arriving guests and ensures all information should be filled on each cards either by Guest Relation Officers or the guests
- Gives the instructions to the Night Reception, during the high occupancy periods, regarding: walk-in guests and release room blocked because of no-shows
- Checks cleanliness of lobby and public areas, lights and as well as front office staff in proper and orderly appearance and behaviour.
- To responsible for front office operation during the absence of Front Office Manager (HO).
- Conducts and ensures the neat of appearance of front office attendant as well as correct attitude and behavior, discusses problems that encountered on this point with front office manager, assistant front office manager and their shift leaders. Co-ordinates with all departments concerned in order to maintain Front Office functions properly

Bharti Airtel Limited

Team Leader • jamshedpur, Jharkhand

- Looking after the MIS & mails.
- · Before & after sales activities.
- · Other miscellaneous duties as assigned
- Handling the data of CRO in the stores
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Collecting the overall performance and managing it as per the company guidelines
- Keeping all the details of customer as per daily walk-in in KIOSK and QMS
- · Daily connection records validation of cashier

01/2017 - 10/2018

- Working as CRO and hence asked to manage the operation as per my performance
- Collective data records of high value customers and providing to the team for operating on it.

ESCORTS POWERTRAC CO. (M/S MAA KARMA TRACTORS DHAMTARI)

Worked as Team Manager • Dhamtari, Chhattisgarh

06/2015 - 11/2016

- · Recruitment Activities
- · Managing all staff's activities.
- · Other miscellaneous duties as assigned
- · preparing reports and financial data
- · Looking after the Mails
- · Before & after sales activities.

Pushpak Management Services Pvt Itd

Administrative Assistant • jamshedpur, Jharkhand

01/2009 - 11/2014

Worked in different Field in This organization at a time with different designation & job responsibility.

for TATA TELESERVICES LTD (Collection department) as Team Leader for 2 year

- Raising Service Request (SR) as customer's Request.
- Looking Billing Problems, .Disputes of Customers .
- Changing the customer billing address.
- Raising request on behalf of customer, when payment made but not reflecting or any other issue.
- Explaining the customer about the tariff plans (Walky and Mobile V-Data Card)

for ICICI BANK LTD (Clearing & Scanning Department) for 2 Years

- Account Opening Form (Saving A/c, Current A/c & NRI A/c) and Web trade Form Scanning (JSR)
- Co-Ordinate with Bankers
- · Looking after the technical issues with Chq
- Encoding
- Chq entry, Payee Name (Outward & Inward).CMS, IPO, Transfer etc.• Co-Ordinate with Bankers• Looking after the Mail & MIS.

for Pushpak Management Services Pvt ltd as an Administrative Assistant for 1 Year

- Managing staff's all over activities
- Looking after the mail & MIS
- · Recruitment Activities
- All Staff's Attendance Activities
- Handling all the issue
- Looking after the sales & purchase in inventory section
- · preparing reports and financial data

Languages

- English
- Chhattisgarhi

Declaration	I solemnly declare that the above information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge. I understand that if any information given above is found false/incorrect, my candidature is liable to be rejected.
Verified by	
	Sigature :
	Place:
	Date :